(Sheldon:)Oh, that's a rather earthy cologne.
(Sheldon:)My uncle used to wear that.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps we can enjoy one last meal
together before Leonard returns.
(Penny:)Yeah, thanks, but I kind of feel
like eating alone tonight, so--
(Sheldon:)Are you sure? With your Italian pizza
and my Chinese noodles,
(Sheldon:)we could play Marco Polo.
(Sheldon:)I mean, of course,
a reenactment of a meal
(Sheldon:)in the life of Marco Polo
the Venetian explorer,
(Sheldon:)not Marco Polo
the terrifying water sport.
(Penny:)Uh, yeah. It sounds fun,
but no thanks.
(Penny:)Have a good night!
(Sheldon:)-What, now, do you have company?
-No. No, no, no.
(Penny:)You know what?
The toilet's been doing that.
-l called the building manager, so--
-Oh, I can take a look at it.
(Scene:)-Well--
-I'm quite familiar with plumbing.
(Sheldon:)Not to brag, but I spent most of
fifth grade with my head in a toilet.
(Penny:)Yeah, no, no, no.
You know what, Sheldon, it's okay.
(Penny:)You don't have to go
into the bathroom.
(Sheldon:)That's curious.
If there's no one here,
(Sheldon:)why are there two glasses
of wine on the table?